You only have three minutes
أمامك ثلاث دقائق فقط
to replace the real Lan Hewei.
لاستبدال لان هيوي الحقيقي.
Later, you find a chance to wake up
لاحقاً، ستجد فرصة للاستيقاظ
and lurk around Lin Mojiao
ويتربصون حول لين موجياو
to finish the plan.
لإتمام الخطة.
Before I met you,
قبل أن ألتقي بك،
my life was always in darkness.
كانت حياتي دائماً في ظلام دامس.
At that time, you were like the sun,
في ذلك الوقت، كنت كالشمس،
warm
دافيء
and dazzling.
ومبهرة.
You don't know
أنت لا تعلم
how important you are to me.
كم أنتِ مهمة بالنسبة لي.
[I never thought someone like you]
لم أتخيل يوماً شخصاً مثلك.
[would fall in love with me without hesitation.]
[سيقع في حبي دون تردد.]
[I know it's painful for you to become a vegetable.]
[أعلم أن تحولك إلى شخص عاجز أمر مؤلم بالنسبة لك.]
[So for me,]
[لذا بالنسبة لي،]
[and for you,]
[ولك أيضاً،]
[just die quietly like this.]
[مت بهدوء هكذا.]
[But Lin Mojiao]
[لكن لين موجياو]
[can't wait to kill me.]
[لا أطيق الانتظار حتى يقتلوني.]
President Lin,
الرئيس لين،
Lanhe Group is waiting.
مجموعة لانهي تنتظر.
I'm not Lan Hewei.
أنا لست لان هيوي.
I'm not trying to take your identity.
أنا لا أحاول انتزاع هويتك.
I never forgot...
لم أنسَ أبداً...
Never.
أبداً.
I'm not Lan Hewei.
أنا لست لان هيوي.
I'm Xu Meng.
أنا شو منغ.
Lan Hewei is my sister.
لان هيوي هي أختي.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
believe it or not,
صدق أو لا تصدق،
I will get you out of there.
سأخرجك من هناك.
Lu Xing, do you want to...
لو شينغ، هل تريد...
Get up.
استيقظ.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Can you hold on?
هل يمكنك الصمود؟
Your opponent is Lin Mojiao.
خصمك هو لين موجياو.
As his wife,
بصفتها زوجته،
you have to be 100% committed to this role
يجب أن تكون ملتزماً بنسبة 100% بهذا الدور
to make him lower his guard.
لجعله يخفف من حذره.
I'm Lin Mojiao now.
أنا الآن لين موجياو.
Use what I taught you.
استخدم ما علمتك إياه.
Relax.
يستريح.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Touch me.
المسني.
Not enough.
غير كافٍ.
That's all you've learned?
هذا كل ما تعلمته؟
That's it for today.
هذا كل شيء لليوم.
I've bought you a ticket back to China tomorrow.
لقد اشتريت لك تذكرة عودة إلى الصين غداً.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أزج بك في هذا الأمر.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
If she knows your identity...
إذا كانت تعرف هويتك...
She will never know.
لن تعرف أبداً.
Sir.
سيد.
Something's wrong.
هناك خطب ما.
Back to China.
العودة إلى الصين.